Inventory of Military Department Records
Connecticut State Library
Military Dept. records
1775-2004
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut.Military Dept
cubic feet
RG013
Multiple
Container List
- Series 1. Old Series, 9999-9999
  - 1. Adjutant General, 1792-1907 (Box 1)
    - General orders, 1792-1831; 6 inches (Box 1)
      - 1792-1823, Bound volume (Box 1)
        Photostat copy in Classified Archives
        [973.9 C762ord 1792-1823]
      - 1815 November 18-1820 September 25, 1 folder (Box 1)
        Organizes individual milita units.
        Chronological
      - 1835 May 12-1836 August 26, 1 folder (Box 1)
        Approves dissolution of individual milita units.
      - Brigade orders, 1839-1841; 1 folder (Box 1)
        Election of officers.
        Unarranged
      - 1815-1831, 3 bundles (Box 1)
    - Resignations and discharges, 1818-1839; 1 foot (Box 6)
    - Annual statistical reports, 1809 October-1820 November; 1 envelope (Box Item 7)
      Men serving in the men serving in the militia, matross (artillery) companies, cavalry and infantry.
      Listed
    - Returns and reports, 1810-1861; 11 feet (Box 8-19)
      From militia units on their composition, officer elections and other activities; orders (or copies) directing them to meet, to elect officers, etc.;notes of receipt and General Assembly approval of returns and reports.
      Roughly chronological
    - Forms listing company roster at the statutory annual May parade, 1858-1860; 3 bundles (6 inches) (Box 20)
    - Annual statistical reports on brigage composition, 1843-1845, 1855-1861; 4 bundles (5 inches) (Box 20)
    - Enrollment reports, 1850-1863; 2 feet (Box 21-22)
      From town clerks or "collectors" certifying the number of men eligible for and exempt from military service.
      Partially chronological by town.
      There are no boxes 23 or 24.
    - Incoming letters, 1834-1889; 22 feet (Box 25-44)
      Chronological with gaps.
      No index appears to exist.
    - Officers' responses to request for recommended uniforms, 1811; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 45)
    - Descriptions of currently used uniforms, 1845; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 45)
    - Mostly miscellaneous and unfiled incoming letters, circa 1815-1830; 1 folder (1 inch) (Box 45)
    - E.W.N. Starr, Adjutant General, 1850 May-1854 May; 1 folder (1 inch) (Box 45)
      Copies or drafts of outgoing letters.
      Presented by his son, F.F. Starr, 1922
    - General orders, 1861-1865; 15 inches (Box 51)
      Printed and manuscript copies of the U.S. and Connecticut commands.
    - Incoming letters and orders, 1861-1865 (Box 52-55)
      - Commander-in-Chief, 1863 June-1866b April
      - United States officers, 1863 July-1866 April
      - Connecticut Militia, 1855 May-1860 December, 1863 July-1866 March
      - Volunteers, 1862 December-1866 May
      - Connecticut National Guard, 1861 May, 1865 April-1866 April
      - Recruiting officers, 1861-1865
    - Table of Volunteer Forces, 1861-1862; .5 inch (Box 56)
      Showing unit strength, officer names, etc.
      By regiment and company.
    - Copies of telegrams sent or received office, 1863 June-1865 December; 3 inches (Box 56)
    - Appointments, promotions, discharges and desertions, 1861-1865; 4 feet (Box 57-60)
      Chronological. Unfiled papers at end.
    - Reports of operations, engagements and casualties, 1860 July-1866 March; 10 inches
      Official Adjutant General's reports indicated with an asterisk. Many of these reports were never reprinted.
    - Reports and rosters, 1861-1865; 17 feet (Box 94-100)
      Partially arranged.
      - Recruits for regiments in the field, 1862-1863
      - Roll of nine-months volunteers not mustered into U.S. service
      - Volunteers recruited in rebel states
      - HQ troops, Department of the Gulf
      - Volunteers and substitutes mustered in (monthly reports)
      - Substitutes, 1864-1865
      - Men furnishing substituted
      - Naval recruits, 1865
      - Conscripts
      - Recruits
      - Volunteers and re-enlisted veterans (payrolls), 1863-1865
      - Deserters from Connecticut regiments
      - Company rolls, 1862
      - Enlistments
      - Rolls of married soldiers
      - New Haven Conscript Camp transfer rolls
      - Morning reports, 1861-1862
    - Returns of enrolled milita, 1861-1863; 1 foot (Box 113)
      By towns.
    - Officer nominations, 1861-1862 (Box 114)
    - Officer commissions revoked and not delivered, undated; 3 inches (Box 114)
    - Certificates of performance of duty, 1864-1865; .5 inch (Box 137)
    - Undeliverable certificates of service, 1923; .25 inch (Box 158)
    - Special orders pertaining to the State Guard, 1940-1953; 3 volumes (8 inches) (Box 170-172)
  - 2. Collector of State Taxes, 1815 March-May; 3 inches (Box 2)
    Lists of persons exempted from military service for each town to the Secretary of the State.
    Unarranged.
  - 3. Militia Organization, 1816 (Box 1)
    - Organization of the militia... (Hartford, 1816), 32 pp.
      Printed pamphelt describing the structure and the scope of individual units including officer lists.
    - Officers' recommendations concerning the organization, 1 folder
    - Instructions and reports on the formation of companies, 1 folder
    - Returns: Stratistical reports on the milita, infantry, cavalry and artillery, 1 folder (1 inch)
  - 4. Governor as Captain General, 1815-1858; 2 feet 6 inches (Box 3-5)
    Petitions for the establishment of new or the reorganization or redefinition of existing units, with related notes and correspondence.
    Roughly chronological.
  - 5-6. Not in use.
  - 7. United States Army, 1807-1808; 2 bundles (4 inches) (Box 8)
    Muster rolls and inspection reports of men detached for service in the United States military, if called.
  - 8-16. Not in use.
  - 17. General and Field officers (Box 45)
    - Resignations and appoints, 1825 May session; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 45)
    - Resignations of men superseded or dailed promotions, 1831; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 45)
  - 18-20. Not in use.
  - 21. Bridgeport "G" Company, 1852-1854; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 45)
    Letters.
  - 22. Court martials, 1810-1860; 1 foot 8 inches
    Proceedings and related papers. Partial list in first box.
    - Trial of Andrew Hull, Jr., 1800 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Joshua King, 1801-1802 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Jonathan Pettibone, 1810 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Adjut. Robert Southworth, 1811 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Zalmon B. Banks, 1813 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Ensign Thomas L. Bevins, 1814 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Liet. Malachi Cooke, 1814 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Lieut. Rufus Coburn, 1814 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Capt. Caleb Thompson, 1814-1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Ensign Robert H. Austin, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Capt. William Beebe, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Quartermaster Isaac Benton, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Capt. Nehemiah Clarke, 1814-1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Ensign Luther Cook, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Lieut. Lulius Griswold, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Lieut. Marvin Griswold, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Capt. David Hall, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Lieut. William Hall, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Capt. Jeremiah Holt, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Trial of Ralph G. Ingersoll, 1815 (Box 46)
    - Statement of Ralph G. Ingersoll (Box 47)
    - Trial of Lieut. Benoni Johnson, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Lieut. Chester Loomis, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Elisha Loomis, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Ensign Reuben Loomis, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Lieut. Warren Loomis, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Joseph Mansfield, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Cornet David McKinney, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Lieut. Stephen Russell, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Ensign Champion Scovill, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Zimri Skinner, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Uriel Tuttle, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Ensign Henry Whittlesey, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Ensign Samuel Wright, 1815 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Samuel Crowell, 1816 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Eli Lacey, 1816 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Ensign Ansel Southworth, 1816 (Box 47)
    - Trial of Capt. Horatio Woodward, 1816-1817 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Amos Bugbee, 1817-1818 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. William Giddings, 1818 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Ensign Alfred Seeley, 1818 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Col. Abel Hall, 1819 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Jabez Ripley, 1819 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Col. Elias Starr, 1819 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Maj. levi Hubbell, 1820 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Lieut. William Kelley, 1820 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Alpheus Shumway, 1820 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Daniel Tracy, 1820 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Gordon Henderson, 1822 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Lieut. Jacob Robinson, 1822 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Samuel Corbin, 1823 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. John Prentis, 1823 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Egbert D. Peck, 1824 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. Alpheus Shumway, 1824 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Lieut. Charles A. Stanley, 1824 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Maj. Robert Knapp, 1824 (Box 48)
    - Trial of Capt. John C. Howard, 1825 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Maj. Robt. Knapp, 1826 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Lieut. Col. Levi Coe, 1828 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Capt. Sidney Bushnell, 1831 (Box 49)
    - Fees, Costs, and Expenses, Court Martial, 1837 (Box 49)
    - Proceedings of Court Martial, 1837 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Ensign Russell Adams, 1837 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Capt. Anthony Roberts, 1837 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Ensign Shelton Smith, 1839 (Box 49)
    - Proceedings of Court Martial, 1842 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Moses W. Comstock, 1842 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Capt. Whiting Wilcox, 1842 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Col. Major C. Peck, 1846 (Box 49)
    - Trial of Capt. Amos Witter, 1847 (Box 49)
    - Unarranged cases, 1810-1862 (Box 50)
  - 23-27. Not in use.
  - 28. Connecticut Volunteer Force, 1862-1866; 1 foot 3 inches (Box 61)
    Deaths, discharges and desertions.
  - 29. Not in use.
  - 30. Connecticut Volunteers Regiments, 1861-1866
    - "List of deceased Connecticut volunteers during the war 1861 to 1866.", 1 volume (1 inche) (Box Item 64)
    - Bound volumes, by regiment, personnel lists and record summaries, brief unit histories, etc., 28 volumes (2 feet 6 inches) (Box Items 65-93)
      "Index" volume at end numerically list each regiment's men.
  - 31-32. Not in use.
  - 33. Town Selectment's Returns, 1862-1864; 2 feet (Box 111-112)
    Volunteers and men drafted.
    By town.
  - 34. Volunteer Reecruiting Service, 1863-1865 (Box 112)
    Consolidated returns.
  - 35. Not in use.
  - 36. Other state regiments, 4 inches (Box 113)
    Connecticut members.
  - 37-38. Not in use.
  - 39. Camp Terry, 1862 (Box 114)
    Guard reports.
  - 40. Deserters, 1862; .5 inch (Box 114)
    Receipts
  - 41. Surgeons, 1862; .5 inch (Box 114)
    Discharge certificiates.
  - 42. Notice, 1861-1863; 3 inches (Box 114)
    Discharge or resignations, acceptances of appointment.
  - 43. Contracts, 1862; 1 inch (Box 115)
    Substitutes and conscripts
  - 44. Stidham's list, 1861-1865; 2 inches (Box 115)
    Officers and men in the U.S. Navy
  - 45. Knight General Hospital, 1863-1865; 4 inches (Box 115)
    Reports.
  - 46. "Petitions, orders, etc.", 1863-1865; 5 inches (Box 115)
  - 47. Provision returns and related papers, 1862-1865; 1 foot (Box 116)
    Includes inventories, inspection reports, etc.
  - 48. "Miscellaneous matter", 1862-1869; 8 inches (Box 117)
  - 49. Pensions, 1864 November-1881 December; 16 feet (Box 118-131)
    Incoming letters.
    Chronological.
  - 50. "Additional Bounty", 1866-1877; 3 feet (Box 132-134)
    Claim letters from soldiers and their heirs, receipts for issued bounty, and rejected claim letters.
    Each group chronological.
  - 51. Testimonial requests, 1868-1871; 2 feet 6 inches (Box 135-136)
    Letters requesting certificates attesting to Civil War service, as provided by General Assembly resolution.
  - 52. Bounties, 1865-1866; 1 envelope (.25 inch) (Box 137)
    Certificates of eligibility.
  - 53. Not in use.
  - 54. Pension Bureau, 1861-1865; 2 inches (Box 137)
    "Additional Wounds" slips, with name and rank of soldier, certificate number, date and nature of wounds, etc.
    Alphabetical by name.
  - 55. Connecticut Volunteer Organizations, 1868-1869; 5 inches (Box 137)
    Letter requesting copies of
    Catalogue of Connecticut Volunteer Organizations...as provided by an Act of the General Assembly
  - 56 Adjutant General, U.S. Army, 9 feet (Box 138-145)
    Forms requesting informatin on Civil War service records for Connecticut citizens, with reply endorsed on the back.
    By organizational unit.
  - 57. Subsistence stores account book, 1899; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box Item 146)
    Listing of quantities and kinds of food received each day, with vendor names. Daily listings of stores distributed to various units.
  - 58. Pension vouchers, 1877-1923 (Box Items 147-151)
    Lists of persons receiving U.S. pensions.
  - 59. Quarter Master General, 1862 April-1863 March; 10 inches (Box 152-153)
    Monthly accounts including schedule summaries, copies of vouchers, receipts, etc. Schedules A-M follow summaries.
  - 60. Orders, reports and other papers, 1891-1897; 1 foot 6 inches (Box 154-156)
    Includes appointments, elections of officers, discharges, morning reports, oaths of office, target practice reports, medical director's reports, etc.
  - 61. Sharpshooters, 1897-1898; 1 foot (Box 157)
    Reports and scores.
  - 62. Officers' reports, 1898; 3 inches (Box 158)
  - 63. Paymaster General, 1865-1874; 4 inches (Box 158)
    Acknowledgement of claims and request.
  - 64. Not in use.
  - 65. Camp Cooke, Niantic, 1897 August; 1 volume (2 inches) (Box Item 159)
    Photographs.
  - 66. National Home for Disabled Volunteer Soldiers, 1867-1880; 1 volume (.25 inches) (Box Item 160)
    List of Connecticut soldiers as patients.
  - 67. Enlisted soldiers, 1863-1865; 2 volumes (2 inches) (Box Items 161-162)
    Name, unit, enlistment date and town of residence.
    Alphabetical.
  - 68. Volunteer Regiments, 1861-1865; 1 volume (2 inches) (Box Item 163)
    Muster rolls as included in draft
    Catalogue of Connecticut Volunteer Organizations...(Hartford, 1869
  - Commissions, 1861-1873; 1 volume (2 inches) (Box Item 164)
    By regiment and unit.
  - 70. Military Emerency Board, 1917-1921; 5 volumes (8 inches) (Box Items 165-169)
    Mimeographed copies of special orders pertaining to the Home Guard (2 volumes), and the State Guard (1 volume); and second set (2 volumes)
  - 71. Civil War Volunteers, 1877-1924; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 173)
    Service Certificates.
  - 72. Not in use.
  - 73. Non-commissioned officers, 1909-1914; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 173)
    Appointments and promotion warrants.
  - 74. Cash book, 1887-1888; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 173)
  - 75. Catalogue of Connecticut Volunteer Organizations, 1869-1888; 2 volumes (1 inch) (Box 173)
  - 76. Record of Service of Connecticut Men...during the War of the Rebellion, 1886-1890; 3 leaflets (.5 inch) (Box 173)
    Accounts most likely kept by Major E.K. Winship, Washington agent.
  - 77. Fitch's Home for the Soldier, Norton Heights, Conn., 1882-1936 (Box 173)
    - Adjutant General's Office list of dishonorable discharges, 1887-1893; 1 envelope (.25 inch) (Box 173)
    - Clothing requisitions, 1886-1887; 5 inches (Box 174)
      Box 174 is now part of Record Group 73, Department of Veterans'Affairs. Location and box number remain the same. For additional records relating to either Fitch's Home or the Veterans Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill) see RG 73.
    - Supply vouchers, 1891; 2 inches (Box 174)
    - Discharges and Disapproved admission applications, 1891-1895; 4 inches (Box 174)
    - Manuscript register nad typed list, 1887-1935; Photostat copies (4 inches) (Box 175-175b)
      Prepared by Charles R. Hales.
  - 78-79. Not in use. (Folder 1)
  - 80. U.S. Navy paymaster, 1864-1874 (Box Items 175 c-r)
    - a. Men's ledger, 1864-1865; 2 volumes
      Non-alphabetical list of names. No index.
    - b. Register of materials received and expended at the U.S. Naval Depot, Bay Point, Port Royal, SC, 1865-1866; 1 volume
    - c. Register of materials received and expended on board U.S. Stores Ship Idaho, Yokohama, Japan, and at U.S. Naval depot, Nagasaki, Japan, 1873-1874; 1 volume
  - First Regiment, Infantry
    - 81. 2nd Flank Company, 1824-1829; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 176)
      Minutes, price list for "tools sold".
    - 82. Three-month enlistees, 1861-1879; 1.5 inches (Box 176)
      Bounty registers, receipts, muster rolls.
    - 83. Col. Lucious A. Barbour, 1880 February - 1884 May; 1 volume (1.5 inches) (Box 176)
      Letterpress copies of outgoing letters.
    - 84. First Connecticut Volunteer Infantry, 1898
      - Roster, 1898; 1 volume (2 inches) (Box Item 177)
      - Scrap book, 1898; 1 volume (3 inches) (Box Item 178)
    - 85. Not in use.
    - 86. First Infantry, Connecticut National Guard, 1905-1925; 1 volume (5 inches) (Box Item 179)
      "History" scrapbook.
    - 87. Approved discharge requests, 1866-1897; 7 inches (Box 180-181)
      Alphabetical by company, followed by Band and Hospital Corps. Also includes transfer requests.
    - 88. Memorial of thanks, 1881; 1 folder (.25 inch) (Box 181)
      Resolution of appreciation for assistance to a t rip to Yorktown, Fort Monroe, VA, Charleston and Columbia, SC, and Washington, DC. Presentation copies.
    - 89. Enrollment registers, 1909-1911; 2 folders (1 inch) (Box 181)
    - 90. Camp Coffin, 1895 August 12-17; 1 volume (.5 inch) (Box 181)
      Guard duty examination reports.
    - 91. Company C, 1871-1880; 4 volumes (4 inches) (Box 182)
      Record books, musters, orders, and target practice.
    - 92. Company F, 1885-1911; 4 volumes (4 inches) (Box 183-186)
      Orders, property books, and marksmen's records.
    - 92a. Company H, 1866-1871; 2 inches (Box 186a)
      Correspondence.
    - 93. Company I, 1878-1881; 1 folder and 5 volumes (5 inches) (Box 187)
      Enlistment papers and record books for musters, orders, target practice and rolls.
    - 94. Company K, 1898-1911
      - Record books, 1878-1911; 5 volumes (Box Items 188-192)
        For special orders, morning reports, marksmanship, and efficiency record.
      - Scrapbooks, 1879-1894; 6 volumes (1 foot 5 inches) (Box Items 193-196, Box 197)
      - World War I, 1917-1919; 13 folders (3 inches) (Box 197)
        General and special orders, instructions, maps, pamphelts, momentos, postcards.
        Donated by Charles B. Yerrington.
        Related artifacts are in the Museum of Connecticut History.
      - Photographs, 1879-1918; 4 volumes and loose material (1 foot) (Box 198)
    - 95-97. Not in use.
  - First Regiment, Heavy Artillery
    - 98. First Regiment, Heavy Artillery, 1861-1865; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box Item 200)
      Published
      Historical rolls...
  - First Regiment, Cavalry
    - 99. First regiment, Cavalry, 1862-1865; 3 folders and 1 volume (3.5 inches) (Box 201 Item 200)
      Muster-in rolls and consolidated morning reports.
  - Second Brigade
    - 100. Second Brigade, 1857-1861; 1 volume (1.5 inches) (Box Item 202a)
      Orders and other related materials.
      Gift of Frank Farnsworth Starr.
  - Second Regiment, Infantry
    - 101. Second Regiment, Infantry, 1861-1897; 5 inches (Box 203)
      Approved discharge requests. Includes transfers, correspondence, and two muster rolls.
      Alphabetical by company, followed by Band and Hospital Corps.
    - 102. Company F (New Haven Grays), 1839-1873; 3 inches (Box 204)
      Record books including accounts, 1839; general records, 1861-1865; and general and special orders, 1863-1873.
    - 103. Company H (Waterbury City Guard), 1854-1860; 1 volume (.5 inche) (Box 204)
      Record book.
  - Second Regiment, Heavy Artillery
    - 104. Second Regiment, Heavy Artillery, 1863-1867; 1 volume (.5 inch) (Box 204)
  - Third Regiment, Infantry
    - 105. Third Regiment, Infantry, 1867-1897; 4 inches (Box 205)
      Approved discharge requests.Also includes transfer requests.
    - 106. Company A, 1873-1886; 5 volumes (5 inches) (Box 206)
      Record books including orders, musters and descriptions, morning reports, and target practice.
    - 107. Company H, 1872-1880; 4 volumes (4 inches) (Box 207)
    - 108. Company K, 1879-1885; 7 volumes (6 inches) (Box 207-208)
      Record books, roll books, muster and descriptive books, special orders, order books, and target practice books.
    - 109. Artillery Company, 1854-1870; .5 inch (Box 208)
      Copies of orders, correspondence, etc., 1854-1856; and Papers relating to John Kelly, 1870.
  - Third Brigade, Signal Corps
    - 110. Roll book, 1893-1897; 1 volume (.5 inch) (Box 208)
  - Fourth Brigade, Infantry
    - 111. Fourth Regiment, Infantry, 1871-1897; 3 inches (Box 209)
      Approved discharge requests. Also includes transfer requests.
      Alphabetical by company, followed by Band and Hospital.
    - Company A (Bethel), 1867-1884; 5 volumes (3 inches) (Box 209-210)
      Record book, muster and descriptive book, roll book.
    - 113. Company C (Stamford), 1872-1881; 4 volumes (4 inches) (Box 210)
      Record book, muister and descirptive book, order book, and target practice book.
    - 114. Company F (Greenwich), 1869-1879; 2 volumes (2 inches) (Box 211)
      Muster and descriptive book, Order book.
    - 115. Company H (Litchfield), 1871-1880
      - Record book, Muster and descriptive book, roll book, order books, target practice record book, 1871-1880; 6 volumes (5 inches) (Box 211-212)
      - Muster rolls, 1861-1865; 1 folder (1 inch) (Box 212)
    - 116. Not in use.
    - 117. Quartermaster, 1861-1862; 4 volumes (4 inches) (Box 213)
      Ledgers and propert books for supplies and equipment charged to individual officers and men.
      Gifts of Lt. G.A. Washburn.
  - Fifth Brigade
    - 118. Brigade record book, 1844-1847; 1 volume (1.5 inches) (Box 214)
      Orders, discharges granted, and orders for election of officers.
  - Fifth Regiment, Infantry
    - 119. Company F (Bridgeport), 1861-1865; 1 volume, 6 folders (5 inches) (Box 215)
      Descriptive book, monthly returns, muster rolls, descriptiove lists, final statements, discharges.
  - Fifth [Independent or "Colored"] Battalion
    - 120. Company A, 1884-1893; 2 volumes (1 inch) (Box 217)
      Rolls books.
    - 121. Company C (Bridgeport), 1879-1890; 11 volumes (7 inches) (Box 217-218)
      Minutes, record book, muster and descriptive book, special order book, roll books, sick book, target practice record book, and property book.
    - 122. Company D (Norwich), 1878-1881; 5 volumes (4 inches) (Box 219)
      Record book, muster and descriptive book, order book, target practice book, and roll book.
  - Sixth Regiment
    - 123. Six Regiment, .5 inch (Box 220)
      Approved discharge requests.
      Alphabetical by company.
    - 124. Company A. Light Infantry (Durham), 2 volumes (1 inch) (Box 220)
    - 123. Second Light Infantry Company (Middletown Cadets), 1838-1840; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 220)
      Record book and scrapbook.
    - 126. Third Company, 1813; 1 volume (.25 inch) (Box 220)
      Orderly book.
    - 126a. Seventh Company, 1822 (Box 220)
      Orderly book. In same volume listed in 126.
    - 127. Company C (Middletown), 1859-1862; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 220)
    - 128. Artillery Company A (Middletown), 1856-1860; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 221)
      Records.
    - 129. Artillery Company B (Middletown), 1847-1856; 1 volume (.5 inch) (Box 221)
  - Seventh Regiment, Infantry
    - 130. First Rifle Company, 1828-1847; Volumes 2 and 3 (1 inch) (Box 221)
      Orderly books.
    - 131. Seventh Company, 1826-1827; 1 volume (.5 inch) (Box 221)
    - 132. Surgeon, 1862-1864; 1 volume (1 inch) (Box 221)
      Dr. George C. Jarvis' register of sick and wounded.